<blog>
	<post>
		<date>December 17, 2022</date>
		<author>Rajesh Dubey</author>
		<title>A Guide To… Titles</title>
		<summary>
            <image_path>https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/175u/2020/theexperimen.jpg</image_path>
            <text>One of the key purposes of  creating great blogs is to build an audience that trusts, believes, and buys from you.</text>
        </summary>
		<body>“Guide” topics work because they promise readers they’ll find all the most important information about a topic. So there’s no need to search for more.
            
            Now, when creating a “guide” headline, be creative! There are many ways to expand on a common “…: A Guide” topic. Create your own unique guide! Here are a few creative blog post title ideas you can use:

            “…: The Only Guide You Need”
            “…: A Step-By-Step Guide”
            “The Advanced Guide To…”
            “A Start-To-Finish Guide…”
            “The In-Depth Guide To…”
            Also, check out the three posts below. Look at the number of shares they got on social media. Aren’t their titles creative?

            The Martin Luther King, Jr. Guide To Inspirational Writing (read).
            How To Use Canva: An 8-Step Guide To Creating Visual Content (read).
            As you can see, there are many ways you can change the common “Guide” title. Remember, expand on your idea!</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>December 16, 2020</date>
		<author>abhishek Sharma</author>
		<title>Speaker</title>
        <summary>
			<image_path>https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/175u/2020/theexperimen.jpg</image_path>
			<text>I once heard a public speaker say that customers don’t buy the product – they buy “why” you made it</text>
		</summary>
		<body>There is a reason why we want more and more infographics: they are fun, quick to read, and easy to remember. If your post has visual content, put it in your headline! The promise of an infographic might result in more people reading your post as well as more shares on social media.
            
            So, why are “Infographic” blog post titles attractive?

            “Infographic” titles attract more people because they promise that the content will be visual, and thus, easy to process and memorize.

            Let’s take a look at three easy ways to inform your readers that there will be an infographic in the post:

            “… (Infographic)”
            “Fun Infographic About…”
            “Infographic: …”</body>
	</post>
    <post>
        <date>December 10, 2020</date>
        <author>Jigar Vaishnav</author>
        <title>“… No One Will Tell You” Blog Post Titles</title>
        <summary>
			<image_path>https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/175u/2020/theexperimen.jpg</image_path>
			<text>One of the key purposes of  creating great blogs is to build an audience that trusts, believes, and buys from you.</text>
		</summary>
        <body>“… No One Will Tell You” title works because it promises you that once you click it, you’ll learn something unknown. Also, you’ll no longer be out of the loop.
            
            Let’s brainstorm for some ideas on how to write creative “… No One Will Tell You” blog post titles that instantly draw people’s attention.

            “What No One Will Tell You But You Need To Hear About…”
            “X Things No One Will Tell You Before…”
            “The… Advice No One Will Give You”
            “X… Secrets No One Has Told You About…”
            “…? Here Are X Realities No One Will Tell You”
            Also, take a look at the three articles below. Can you resist reading them?

            5 Things No One Will Tell You About Your First Job (read).
            6 Things No One Tells You About Running a Business While Traveling Full Time (read).
            Now, let’s try to create a perfect “… No One Will Tell You” title. What would you say about a topic involving fauna and flora? Let’s narrow it down to insects.</body>
    </post>
</blog>
